<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tags on austin norris</title>
    <link>https://acn.dev/tags/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tags on austin norris</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://acn.dev/tags/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A quick problem solved with Python</title>
      <link>https://acn.dev/a-quick-problem-solved-with-python/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 23:07:55 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acn.dev/a-quick-problem-solved-with-python/</guid>
      <description>A coworker was recently working on some hardware in the lab. Particularly, obtaining signal measurements for an experimental magnetometer. It turns out audio analyzers make great tools for the job, and this model (QuantAsylum QA402) helpfully exposes a REST API for controlling the unit and obtaining the raw channel measurement data. The goal in this case was to get the raw signal data into Python for analysis.
One small obstacle: the included software (and bundled webserver) were running on a Windows workstation at the lab bench, and we wanted to be able to run tests and obtain signals remotely.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>How this site works</title>
      <link>https://acn.dev/how-this-site-works/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 22:21:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acn.dev/how-this-site-works/</guid>
      <description>This post describes how I set up this site and some of the pitfalls along the way.  to err is human, or: make sure your CI/CD stages respect git submodules
  The Short Version This site is created using the Hugo static site generator, with the minimalist Etch theme by Lukas Joswiak. The website itself is hosted on GitHub Pages and I manage the domain through Google Domains. A private GitHub repository contains the markdown, config, and static resources, while a GitHub Actions workflow automatically builds and deploys the site to a public repo whenever I push to main.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello</title>
      <link>https://acn.dev/hello/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2021 16:05:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acn.dev/hello/</guid>
      <description>This will be a space for me to document various things I&amp;rsquo;m working on or learning and perhaps the occasional navel-gazing insight. You can find more about me here.</description>
    </item>
    
    
    
    
  </channel>
</rss>
